<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>neptro</title><link>https://netro.xyz/</link><description>Recent content on neptro</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 16:00:39 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://netro.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>bhaktapur</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/bhaktapur/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 16:15:33 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/bhaktapur/</guid><description>Bhaktapur is a small city located on outskirts of the KTM valley. Known for its well preserved Malla dynasty architecture and immaculate temples. It is a heavily trafficked location with a steady flow of both locals and tourists. Determining which group I fall under is an existential dread for another day.
A lot of travel guides online describe Bhaktapur as a city &amp;ldquo;frozen in time&amp;rdquo; but I&amp;rsquo;m not a big fan of this descriptor because I feel like it discounts everyday people that are carrying on their normal lives within the city.</description></item><item><title>riding a bike</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/riding-a-bike/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Feb 2022 11:49:52 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/riding-a-bike/</guid><description>Moving around KTM, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice an immense density of motorbikes. Most are trudging along at a snail&amp;rsquo;s pace beside the slow moving traffic. Others are weaving in and out through any openings on the road. Lanes are an artificial construct and often times, you&amp;rsquo;ll see oncoming traffic on the right side (Nepal is a lefty country) due to overflow.
My cousin described driving in Nepal as a real life video game as your sole focus becomes to navigate through the tiniest of streets and avoid any dynamic obstacles on the road.</description></item><item><title>the weary road</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/the-weary-road/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 09:00:45 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/the-weary-road/</guid><description>Every time I visit Nepal, I make my customary trek from Butwal to Tansen. The entire journey is just 43.1 km or 26 miles for folks at home. However, the trip takes well over two hours because the road meanders beside sheer cliffs the whole time and is heavily trafficked leading to minor congestions and extreme wear. For reference, traveling 48 km (30 miles) back in VA took me roughly 45 minutes.</description></item><item><title>phone number store</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/phone-number-store/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 18:33:57 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/phone-number-store/</guid><description>Getting a new phone number is fairly easy in Nepal. You can go to any authorized seller and pick up a sim card after filling out a single page form. After an hour, your new phone number will be registered with Nepal Telecom and you can make and receive calls as you please. A pretty standard process however my experience inside this one phone number store in Dillibazar was anything but.</description></item><item><title>journeys</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/journeys/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 01:10:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/journeys/</guid><description>When I told my cousin about a half baked idea to go live in Nepal for a few months on our amtrak up to NYC, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t thinking that six months later I would be on stuck in Doha for eight hours well on my way to KTM.
The first 12 hours of the trip from IAD was unexpectedly pleasant. The real fun started as soon as I landed in Doha.</description></item><item><title>neptro.xyz</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/neptro-xyz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:11:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/neptro-xyz/</guid><description>Using this site to blog about my experience in Nepal as I get acclimated to the culture and environment.
Coming to you live... in 51 days</description></item><item><title>Custom URL Page</title><link>https://netro.xyz/my-custom-url/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Sep 2020 16:00:39 -0400</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/my-custom-url/</guid><description>“Look again at that dot. That's here. That's home. That's us. On it everyone you love, everyone you know, everyone you ever heard of, every human being who ever was, lived out their lives. The aggregate of our joy and suffering, thousands of confident religions, ideologies, and economic doctrines, every hunter and forager, every hero and coward, every creator and destroyer of civilization, every king and peasant, every young couple in love, every mother and father, hopeful child, inventor and explorer, every teacher of morals, every corrupt politician, every &amp;quot;superstar,&amp;quot; every &amp;quot;supreme leader,&amp;quot; every saint and sinner in the history of our species lived there-on a mote of dust suspended in a sunbeam.</description></item></channel></rss>