<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Entries on neptro</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/</link><description>Recent content in Entries on neptro</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 09:00:45 +0545</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://netro.xyz/entries/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>the weary road</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/the-weary-road/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 09:00:45 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/the-weary-road/</guid><description>Every time I visit Nepal, I make my customary trek from Butwal to Tansen. The entire journey is just 43.1 km (or 26 miles for folks at home) however the trip takes well over two hours because the road meanders beside sheer cliffs the whole time and is heavily trafficked leading to minor congestions and extreme wear. For reference, traveling 48 km (30 miles) back in VA took me roughly 45 minutes on average.</description></item><item><title>phone number store</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/phone-number-store/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 Jan 2022 18:33:57 +0545</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/phone-number-store/</guid><description>Getting a new phone number is fairly easy in Nepal. You can go to any authorized seller and pick up a sim card after filling out a single page form. After an hour, your new phone number will be registered with Nepal Telecom and you can make and receive calls as you please. A pretty standard process however my experience inside this one phone number store in Dillibazar was anything but.</description></item><item><title>journeys</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/journeys/</link><pubDate>Thu, 20 Jan 2022 01:10:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/journeys/</guid><description>When I told my cousin about a half baked idea to go live in Nepal for a few months on our amtrak up to NYC, I wasn&amp;rsquo;t thinking that six months later I would be on stuck in Doha for eight hours well on my way to KTM.
The first 12 hours of the trip from IAD was unexpectedly pleasant. The real fun started as soon as I landed in Doha.</description></item><item><title>neptro.xyz</title><link>https://netro.xyz/entries/neptro-xyz/</link><pubDate>Mon, 29 Nov 2021 21:11:14 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://netro.xyz/entries/neptro-xyz/</guid><description>Using this site to blog about my experience in Nepal as I get acclimated to the culture and environment.
Coming to you live... in 51 days</description></item></channel></rss>